http://www.handdryer.com/pages/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy notice is in relation to the following sites: handdryer.com and babychangingstationsonline.com
Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:
How To Contact Us
Our Commitment To Privacy:
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Allied Hand Dryer website. On our contact page, we make it possible for you to request that we contact you regarding your need for hand dryers and baby changing stations or for more information about our company. The personal and business information we collect on this page, is:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Website address
Type of services you require
Space for you to make comments
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide solely to contact you. We do not share this information with outside parties. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above.
Our Commitment To Data Security:
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How To Contact Us:
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 800-535-4393 or send us an email at handdryer@hotmail.com.
FIRST IN SERVICE, PRICE & PRODUCTS
Allied Hand Dryer was started in August of 1988 by Darrell Kirksey. He supplied hand dryers and repair services to numerous businesses in and around the South Texas/San Antonio region. Since this time Allied Hand Dryer has grown to become a major distributor of hand dryers, hand dryer parts, and baby changing stations to businesses, schools and government entities around the world.*Free shipping available only in the contiguous U.S. and is not available in AK, HI and Puerto Rico.
INFORMATION
About UsBlogContact UsPrice GuaranteeShipping & ReturnsPrivacy PolicyTerms & Conditions
MY ACCOUNT
RegisterLoginOrder Status
GOT A QUESTION?… CONTACT US NOW
Talk(800) 535-4393(210) 733-5918Fax(210) 308-5924Emailsales@handdryer.comAddress706 West Summit AvenueSan Antonio, Texas 78212
Copyright © 2020 Allied Hand Dryer.
Digital Marketing by Pear Analytics
Added to your cart:
Subtotal
